revenuegateway.com 2011-06-30

# :: Revenue Gateway :: Privacy Policy

When you submit information to REVENUE GATEWAY to make a payment or open an account, we may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, address, email address, credit card number. We do not knowingly collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen.

**Web Site Usage Information**  
We automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you access any of our online services. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our Web sites on an aggregate basis, including but not limited to the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each web page, and the length of their visits.

**How We Use Information Collected**  
We may use information in the following ways: For the purposes you specifically provided the information including, for example, enabling us to process, validate and verify purchases. To register you as a client and establish an account for you. To send you email notifications about our new or existing REVENUE GATEWAY products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you. To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services. To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns. To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences. To allow 3rd party companies to send the client emails promoting other goods and services. 

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example to protect our intellectual property rights). We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law may require us to do so.

**Cookies**  
We define a cookie as any string of data that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our online services. REVENUE GATEWAY employs cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our web servers. This information enables us to deliver faster service to our subscribers, prevent denial of service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our partners. All REVENUE GATEWAY cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to REVENUE GATEWAY web servers, and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information. 

**Security**  
The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. We retain personally identifiable information only as long as necessary to complete a purchase, thwart fraud, provide customer service, or maintain your account with us. 

**Policy Modifications**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. 

**Comments and Questions**  
If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us Here. 

This policy was last updated 15 August 2008.

### Revenuegateway Launches New Exclusives

Converts on the 2nd page  
This campaign is available for banner, Email, Search  
No Incentivized traffic  
US traffic Only 

Converts after a $5.95 S&H  
This campaign is available for banner, Search  
No Incentivized traffic  
US traffic Only
